onebiz.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy | OneBiz.com

## Privacy and data protection

At OneBiz.com AG the protection and security of your private sphere and that of your date plays a large role. Below you will find our guidelines concerning the protection of your personal data. Please read the following information carefully.

## Privacy policy of OneBiz.com AG

OneBiz.com AG respects your privacy. Within the scope of our global company operations we will collect, store and utilize your personal data for precisely specified purposes. We will utilize your data to support and expand our business relations with you, for instance to process your orders, service and support efforts, or to provide offers and information about products, services or the company. We will not sell your data to third parties. Under certain circumstances, we will share summarized online preferences with our ad partners on OneBiz.com AG’s websites. If we share your personal data with third parties outside of our company structure (OneBiz.com), we will inform you about the way in which your data will be shared. We will share your data exclusively with partners, who just like OneBiz.com AG are taking your privacy absolutely seriously. If you have questions or concerns regarding privacy and data proection then simply contact OneBiz.com AG. You may also request your personal data which is stored with OneBiz.com AG so you can add, correct or delete parts of it. We are guaranteeing appropriate measures and processes to assure your personal data.

## The kind of information that will be stored.

OneBiz AG collects certain personal data. This concerns information which is necessary to process orders, deliver services make our website user friendly, respond to requests, improve our relationship to you as a customer, support you with technical difficulties or contact you whenever you wish. OneBiz.com AG may always store data while you are interacting with our business. This happens for instance through the following activities..

  * You registering on our website (OneBiz.com AG) or that of one of our partners.
  * You requesting an offer from us.
  * You placing an order with us.
  * You requesting an email notification with us.
  * You ask one of our online consultants for assistance.
  * You make a support request either online or offline.
  * You transmit your feedback as part of one of our surveys.
  * You will take advantage of special offers.
  * You subscribe to one of our publications, a newsletter or a mailing list.
  * You visit one of OneBiz.com AG’s websites or that of a partner.

If you get in touch with our company, we may ask you for the following information: name, address, email address, online preferences, phone number, activity, industry, transaction related data, customer number, service tag number, service history, credit card data and other bank data, recommendations as well as further information which will be required for the processing of your order or request. We may collect data in relation to you online interactions with our company (such as the sites visited by you, links and ads clicked by you). This data supports us in making the contents, services and marketing materials of our website as relevant to you as a OneBiz.com AG customer as possible. We may show you recommendations based on your browser history and purchase history and send you individually adjusted mailings through various communication channels such as Email.

## OneBiz.com AG utilizes your data for certain purposes.

The transmitted data will be treated responsibly. The data will be utilized for the following general purposes or other lawful business purposes.

  * Processing of your order or delivery of your requested services.
  * Filling of your product and service requests.
  * Improval of our products and services.
  * Establishing contact with you.
  * Individual set up of our communication with you as well as the advertised marketing materials.
  * Support of our business partners in the transmission of individually tailored content.
  * Administration of our common partnership.

## Newsletter, Mailing List, Information Requests.

We or other business units by OneBiz.com AG (or third parties operating on behalf of OneBiz.com AG) send information about our diverse product and service range based on your chosen options. Such information may contain hints about product upgrades, articles in your shopping cart, special offers, updated information, as well as new offers by OneBiz.com AG. These direct messages will only be sent by OneBiz.com AG (or one of OneBiz.com AG’s third party partners). If you do not wish to receive this information then inform us of the following.  
 **Enter the following information and send the applicable message to the address (or fax) mentioned below:** Contact  
Name of the business (if applicable)  
Complete address  
Fax (if applicable)

**Postal address:**  
OneBiz.com AG - Ad objection  
Email: Please [click here](mailto:support@onebiz.com?subject=Unsubscribe) to unsubscribe. .

It may take up to ten working days until your changes are processed. Some sendings such as direct mailing catalogues have been developed in advance and made ready for delivery, you may receive additional information, depending on how you transmitted your request.

## Transfer of personal data.

Your data may be transferred to other company units within OneBiz.com AG, to third parties operating on behalf of OneBiz.com AG or to contract partners of OneBiz.com AG, such as service providers, marketing partners or financial institutes, which share data for OneBiz.com AG. OneBiz.com AG ensures that your data will only be used for the services which this company or partners of OneBiz.com AG deliver, and that all such data will be dealt with in a responsible way. OneBiz.com AG may share your data within applicable areas of law, if the decision of a court or authority demands it, or to ensure that we are abiding by the law. if necessary, OneBiz.com AG may share your personal data with other members of the OneBiz.com AG business group, such as OneBiz.com AG Inc. in the USA or to third party suppliers. We possess the necessary contractual agreements with relevant partner companies to ensure adequate protection of your data.

## Your rights:

Upon request, we will inform you within appropriate deadlines about the way of storing your data, the purpose of storing your data as well as potential recipients of your data or types of recipients and the origin of data. We will complete, correct, delete or block your personal data based on written request and within appropriate deadlines, if such data is shown to be false, incomplete or irrelevant for the purpose of processing.

## Internet trade:

The online shop at www.OneBiz.com contains various options for the processing of your credit card data, your names, your addresses and your email addresses as well as other data supplied by you. OneBiz.com AG will strictly surveil the secure storage of all customer data on our website. We utilize the industry standard SSL security certificate. This standard is available through your browser (for security purposes, more information about these security measures may be found on OneBiz.com’s shop website). If you do not wish to share your credit card data during your online transaction you also may process this transaction without giving such information, and one of our employees will then follow up with you. Alternatively you may reach out to one of our sales representatives via phone. Generally we always try to help our customers with their order problems or to contact them within the framework of our company communication guidelines during orders.

## Individual adjustment:

through usage of certain technologies we will provide the visitors of our websites with individualized content. At OneBiz.com AG we may utilize cookies by OneBiz.com AG or third party suppliers to discover what information may be of interest for you and about how relevant such information is within the frame of your interaction with our company in order to make your experience userfirnedly. With the help of cookies we would like to adjust ourselves to your preferences when visiting the website at [www.OneBiz.com](http://www.onebiz.com/) and to send you individually adjusted messages about products and services by OneBiz.com AG. Click here to receive more information about how we utilize cookies and how to delete cookies or how to refuse cookies.

## Web Beacons

We or third parties who are acting in our name, may utilize web beacons or similar technologies in our messages, websites or within OneBiz.com AG’s messages which you receive from third parties. A web beacon is an electronic image with which a cookie may be recognized on your system if you are visiting a website or requesting an online message. Due to web beacons, we are able to measure the activity of our website and our interaction with you in various ways. This occurs through counting of people who are visiting our website through certain messages or after making a purchase on our website after clicking through a message. In addition we analyze whenever a website is being visited and a description of the website that contains the web becaon image will be made ready. Web beacons also enable us to measure the effectiveness of our messaging campaigns, such as through counting the peoplpe who are viewing a message or becoming active on it, or through research, when a message is being opened and how often it is being shared. The collected data may contain person specific data and using web beacons we may recognize user’s access to cookies that are provided by OneBiz.com AG. In addition we are authorized to combine the collected information with other personal data which we have collected from you. All this information is used to make our contact with you more individual. If necessary we will also utilize this information for other purposes, such as to adjust content on our websites, to offer a shopping cart, or to run internal analysis. Personal data, which is recorded through OneBiz.com AG web beacons will not be shared with third parties, with the exception of service providers who are acting in our name and who are bound by contract not to utilize the information for any other purposes or to make it public. Third parties may place their own web beacons or ads on our websites, as long as they are determined to ensure user’s privacy and data protection. Through the refusal of cookies you may neutralize certain web beacons.

## Websites by third parties.

We would like to make you aware, that other websites, including those which can be visited through our website using hyperlinks, also may register personal data about you. Our privacy protection clause does not apply to the utilization of data on this website or websites linked with [www.OneBiz.com](http://www.onebiz.com/)

### **Privacy Policy for Usage of Facebook-Plugins (Like-Button)**

Privacy Policy for Usage of Facebook-Plugins (Like-Button) Our pages integrate plugins of the social network Facebook, 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. You can identify the Facebook plugin by the Facebook logo or the "Like-Button" ("Like") on our site. You can find an overview of Facebook-plugins here: <http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/> . When you visit our pages, the plugin establishes a connection between your browser and the Facebook server. Facebook thereby obtains, through this information, that you have visited our website with your IP Address. If you click on the Facebook "Like" button while you are logged into your Facebook account, you can link the content of our pages to your Facebook profile. Facebook can thereby correlate your visit of our site with your user account. We point out that we as providers of the sites have no knowledge of the content of the data being transmitted as well as their use through Facebook. For more information, please refer to the privacy statement of facebook under <http://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php> .  
If you do not wish that Facebook assign your visit to our site with your Facebook-account, please log out from your Facebook account.

### **Privacy Statement for the Use of Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer and which enable an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.

Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity for website operators and provide others with website and internet related services. In addition, Google may also transfer this information to third parties where this is required by law or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with other data of Google Inc.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, we point out that you may not be able to use all functions of this website in this case. By using this site, you agree to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described for the aforementioned purposes above.

### **Privacy Statement for using Google +1**

**Collection and dissemination of information:**

With the Google +1 button you can publish information worldwide. Through the Google +1 button you and other users receive personalized content from Google and our partners. Google will store both the information that you have given for a content +1, as well as information about the page that you viewed when you click on +1. Your +1' s can be shown as evidence along with your name and profile photo in Google services, such as in search results or in your Google profile, or elsewhere on websites and ads on the internet. Google records information about your +1-activities to improve Google's services for you and others. In order to use the Google +1 button, you need a globally visible, public Google profile, which must contain at least the chosen name for the profile. This name is used in all Google services. In some cases, this name can also substitute any other name that you used when sharing content under your Google account. The identity of your Google profile can be shown to users who know your e-mail address or other identifying information about you.

**Using the information collected:**

The information you provide in accordance with the applicable Google privacy policy will be used in addition to the above uses. Google may release aggregate statistics on the +1-activities of the user and forward them to users and partners such as publishers, advertisers or linked sites.

### Privacy Statement for the Use of Twitter

Twitter service functions are integrated on our website. These functions are offered by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. Through the use of Twitter and function of "re-tweet" the web pages you visit are linked to your Twitter account and made known to other users. This data is also transmitted to Twitter. We point out that we as providers of the sites have no knowledge of the content of the transmitted data as well as their use obtained through Twitter. For more information, please refer to the privacy statement of Twitter at <http://twitter.com/privacy>. you can change your Twitter privacy preferences in the account settings under <http://twitter.com/account/settings>.

## Additional information:

If you have asked to be contacted through a OneBiz.com AG partner we must share contact details with said partner. This information will not be shared with anyone and this partner will only receive it for the purpose of connecting with you. Your personal data which is registered by us will be stored and processed. in accordance with data protection policies of OneBiz.com AG. If you would like to establish contact with us or you have questions regarding our data protection policy, send an email to [support@onebiz.com](mailto:support@onebiz.com) Date of coming into effect: March 2014
